You
I'm always searching
I've always been searching.
Hmm.
That's unlucky.
I got one with kelp.
They're all filled with kelp today.
Huh? Why'd you do that, Akane?
I told you 10,000 times.
Tuna mayo.
I like kelp.
That's right.
You lost to Aoi, man.
Yeah, even though you said it 10,000 times.
You shut up.
Come on. Time to practice.
Huh?
Hold on. I'm not done eating yet.
Hurry up and finish.
My Akane special's sounding freaking awesome.
What a dumb name.
Huh?
Hey, I...
I wanna play.
Yeah?
Want me to teach you a little guitar?
So?
What do you wanna play?
Huh?
Huh? What? For real?
Oh, man, that's adorable.
You must really look up to me, huh, kiddo?
No!
Not a chance.
But girl bass players are pretty cool.
For sure.
Okay, then, Al.
You're gonna grow up and become our bassist.
What?
Hey, what'll happen to me?
Sounds fun, huh, Aoi?
I don't know, Abo.
You'll sing backup.
What?
Or you could be our dancer.
Jeez, Pomba, you really...
Stop, stop.
What happened to practicing?
What should we play?
Uh...
Hmm.
Akane?
Play the usual.
There you go.
That one again.
Count us off, Michinko.
If you say so.
Hey, wait a second.
Come on, I said wait!
Pomba, your mic's not plugged in.
Really?
Okay, are we ready?
If you can get there...
But...
Sometimes...
Just seems too far away.
A terrible accident.
They were both in the car.
I heard the other driver was distracted.
Two toddlers left to fend for themselves.
It's just so horrible.
Akane's a senior in high school, right?
What'll they do?
Little one, be sure to listen to your sister, okay?
You girls will have to really work together from now on.
I don't think I can go.
Why?
What do you mean?
We're not moving to Tokyo together?
Akane!
Hey, stop bullying Akane, butthead!
Awe!
Don't take her away!
Me be fatty!
Fatty?
My body fat's only 7%, you know.
Shut up, Fatty!
Stinky gorilla!
You can't take Akane away!
Akane stays with me!
So I'm still searching.
You can't take it.
Wooohoo!
Woooo!
Woohoo!
Wooo!
I'm searching for that place where all my dreams will come true.
Hey, what's up?
I'm moving to Tokyo.
I certainly see the appeal.
But this wouldn't be for university, right?
You'll be working?
Well, yeah.
At least until my band hits the big time.
Your band, huh?
How many members?
What members?
It's only me.
Sounds like you'll be keeping that day job.
Okay, next.
Otaki, come on in.
Yes, sir.
Oh, she's the coolest.
Otaki, hurry up.
So, my career plan is I'm gonna get married.
Woo!
I haven't exactly found Mr. Hart yet, but...
Alright, so you'll be working.
Got it.
Okay, next.
I wanted to talk about my plan.
Thank you, my boy.
We're starting to prepare for the end of year festival, so City Hall's getting pretty busy.
I might not be able to pick you up next month.
Ugh.
You expect me to waste an hour of my life walking to and from school every day?
Well, it's the right season for it.
It's nice to walk through the mountains and see the leaves change.
Ugh.
I really hate the mountains.
Oh?
Living in a mountain valley basically just means you're walled in.
It's like we're prisoners being held in a giant jail.
My gosh.
Here we go again with the teen angst.
Whatever you want to call it.
Doesn't matter because I'm getting the heck out of this town.
Hang on.
Good afternoon.
Hello.
Lovely to see you, Akane.
Aoi.
Welcome back.
What are you up to?
Oh, well, Masamichi invited too many people for tonight's assembly.
So we ended up borrowing some seat cushions and tables from Yamaguchi.
Oh, let me help you with that.
There's no need to put yourself out.
Come help, Aoi.
We don't want to hold you up on your way home.
Not at all.
I'm also going to the assembly.
Oh, right.
Hey, want some of these pairs?
Really?
I'd love some.
Thank you so much.
You've got such a sweet big sister.
You should be grateful for her, Aoi.
Being told to be grateful all the time...
It just makes me want to rebel even more.
No, listen to me.
A miso potato stall really needs to have a variety of flavor options.
We could add yuzu or chili pepper to the miso.
You think something like this will actually draw a crowd?
Hey, have a little more faith in this, buddy.
There are so many nice tourist spots around here, but people always stay in the city.
We need something big if we want to break through and attract attention.
Exactly.
We should try and ride this way.
Masamichi from the tourism division did us a favor.
Yeah.
And we don't want to waste the opportunity.
You know, over at city hall, there's a rumor that he moved around a lot of money for this.
Stop spreading lies, Akane!
You gonna perform, Aoi?
The moment my music starts being used to revitalize the town is when it stops being music.
Instead of something enjoyable, it'll become the acoustic representation of my suffering.
I'm sure you think you said something super deep and profound just now, but I promise you didn't.
But anyway, the music's gonna bring people in and transform this town.
Aoi! Tsugu!
Hm? Dad?
Uh, so are you gonna be rocking out over at the shrine hall tonight?
Yeah.
Wrap it up before nine, okay?
Hearing bass music on the wind gives me the heebie-jeebies that late at night.
You know, there's a soundproof room in our house.
What?
Haven't you ever wanted a big brother?
Dad, please, at least try to play it cool.
I'm not gonna set my sister up with a divorcee.
Hey, now! I was the one who got cheated on! I'm an honest and faithful divorcee!
Who cares?
Hey!
Hey, Aoi!
Yeah?
Do you remember our old buddy Shino?
Uh, kind of? Why?
No, nothing. It's totally fine if you don't.
Hmph.
Hmm.
About what my dad said earlier.
It's not like I'm taking his side or anything.
But he is actually serious about...
Can you refrain from talking about that in here, please?
So it's okay to talk about it elsewhere?
It's not okay.
But... better than in here.
No, not like that. Look, you gotta press down harder.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Whoa, wow. I just noticed that... you got a birthmark in your eye.
Hey, look.
Me too.
They say eye birthmarks mean you're destined for stardom.
You and I are both eyeball stars.
Oh, eyeball stars!
What kind of name is that? That's so random.
I don't know.
It's not funny. Cut it out. It's a cool name.
Cool luck name!
Whoa! Wasn't Donkichi Nitobe on the New Year's Eve special a while back?
Oh, now I remember him. Didn't he ride on that sparkly portable shrine?
Yeah! I do remember seeing that.
We've asked him to compose a song for our town and perform it at the festival.
What if he writes about fireworks exploding and then we could, like, set some off?
Fireworks? Awesome.
Guess you moved some serious money around after all, huh?
Listen. The stakes are high here.
Because, well, I... see, my own life happens to be on the line.
So I'm really counting on your help with this event, Hakane.
Huh?
I've already arranged it with the Citizens Affairs Division.
I heard about that. Break a leg.
I'm sure it'll be great.
Wait, what?
We're about to get started.
All right, then. We'll hash out the details later.
Wait, Michinko!
Well, looks like our department does have some pull.
Good luck with that.
Michinko has a giant crush on you. You know that, right?
Mm-hmm. I've noticed.
Great, so don't do anything that might give him false hope.
He's my childhood friend. And now my coworker.
With relationships, sometimes you have to leave things alone, even if they're really obvious.
That's the adult way to handle it.
Gosh, adults are so boring.
More importantly...
Hm?
Have you maybe given it some more thought?
What?
Going to college.
It's not like you can't play in a band and be a student.
Stop. We've gone over this.
You promised you wouldn't bring it up anymore.
Hm.
So cut it out.
Don't break your promise.
Well, I'm off to practice.
Okay.
So...
What?
Mm-hm.
You go.
We'll be right back.
No, stop!
What the heck is the matter with you?
You've got zero sense of rhythm.
You're way off beat.
Huh?
Hmm?
Who are you?
What?
Hey.
You and I are eyeball stars.
Shin-no?
Hmm?
How do you know...
Wait, that's the school's uniform.
Hey, are you one of my fans?
Want to shake hands?
So...
What?
Hmm.
You really are, Shin-no?
Yeah, that's what I'm telling you.
And you are...
Hey, stop!
Wait up!
Hang on a minute!
Hey!
What the hell is going on?
Let me out of here!
Ah, Akane!
You're back?
Already done with practice?
I'm making your favorite tonight.
Ground meat cutlets.
Shin-no just...
Sorry.
Tell me...
What happened with Shin-no?
Uh...
Well, uh...
Right, I just thought of him while I was practicing.
And I was wondering...
Um...
What he's up to these days.
We fell out of contact a long time ago.
You know, he...
Well, he could be dead for all I know.
Oh, yeah.
That's a total possibility.
The only possibility, right?
I mean...
He looks like he hasn't aged at all.
Are we?
Hey!
Looks like you left the front door open!
That's very dangerous.
Michinko?
Akane!
What are you two still doing here?
What does he mean?
Wait...
Whatever!
There's no time!
Huh?
You gotta help with this thing!
Yeah, we talked about this.
Oh, did I forget to tell you about the thing today?
Today?
Ah!
It doesn't matter!
Just come with me!
Right when he steps out, we open it.
And try to look cheerful, okay?
Dad, did you really spend all night making this thing?
Hey!
Don't spill any miso on it!
So pointless.
I don't even have time for this stuff.
Wait, why is he coming today?
Isn't the event a week from now?
Well, yeah, but Nitobe is legendary for writing songs about specific towns, and he says he needs to try all the local foods and get to know the people to feel the warmth of the town and sing directly to the soul of the area.
And City Hall is gonna pay for all that?
Yeah!
So this guy's basically a freeloader.
Sugu?
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you so very much for waiting.
The one and only Dunkin' Itobe has arrived.
I've come from far, far away.
I've crossed plains and mountains just for the pleasure of putting a smile on all of your faces.
What?
No.
Oh, Dunkin' Itobe!
What's so true?
Really?
No.
Hmm?
Makanu?
Uh...
Shin-Pet...
Shin-No...
Come on, Tsugu!
Hold it the right way!
What?
Oh, wait!
Gah...
Mom...
Dad...
...and all of my ancestors...
...hunt me your strength!
Oh, hey...
...I got a receipt, so do you...
...huh?
Wait...
...so was that...
...Shino guy really there after all?
Yeah...
...I was sure he was a ghost...
...but then...
...we saw the real Shin-No at the station...
...so the one I saw earlier...
...Doppelganger?
I don't know!
But I'm sure that was Shin-No too!
I don't get it, but there's definitely something weird going on!
See anything?
Hmm...
There's no one in here...
Huh?
That can't be true...
Hey, what gives?
Huh...
...you ran scared!
Yeah!
Hey, you let her go!
Huh?
What's this kid?
Looks just like Machinko!
Tell us who you are right now!
I already told you who I am!
I'm Shino!
Who the heck are you?
It's time to run, Ao!
What?
Okay?
Did you...
...say Ao?
I'm Aoi...
Aoi...
...Aoi...
...Aibo Star...
...Number Two!
Huh?
That day...
...when Akane told me she wasn't coming to Tokyo...
...I just couldn't make myself leave...
...So I stayed in here...
...thinking things over...
...and...
...before I knew it...
...uh...
...it was the morning?
Why is that a question?
Well, I don't get it either!
I just started to nod off...
...so I laid down right there...
...and then this awful noise woke me up!
Awful?!
...
...It didn't really seem like anything happened...
...but here you are telling me it's been 13 years...
...it doesn't feel real...
Oh yeah...
...just like Rip Van Winkle...
...So wait...
...does that mean...
Anyway...
...there's no use sitting around crying over all the time I've lost...
How are you accepting this so fast?
I mean...
...it's all thanks to you guys...
...you two make coping easy...
...man, you really are a mini version of Machinko, huh?
Read the room...
Whatever he is...
...I'm sure it isn't a ghost...
...his body's tangible...
Uh...
...okay...
...but then...
...hmm...
...a living spirit?
A living spirit?
People...
...have told tales...
...about how if you have strong feelings for someone...
...you can unconsciously send a living spirit of yourself to be with them...
I've heard of that...
...some people do that to curse or kill someone...
...oh...
...and, uh...
...Shino did get dumped by Akane...
...maybe this spirit was created out of that regret...
...what are you saying?
Huh?
I have no regrets...
...because I haven't given up on anything yet...
...what?
I've thought it over and made my decision...
...I'm gonna move to Tokyo...
...I'm gonna become a big-time musician...
...and then...
...I'll make a glorious return to be with Akane!
What's with the crazy optimism?
Oh no!
Why do bad things always happen to good people?
Akane...
...must be 31 now...
...so...
...31 and...
...30...
...uh...
...wait...
...Akane isn't married, right?
Right.
Awesome!
I mean...
...I guess I shouldn't be happy about that...
...doesn't matter...
...hurry up and marry her.
You wanna...
...meet her?
You idiot!
I can't meet her yet!
You're an idiot!
Have you not been listening this whole time?
I need to become a big-time musician first!
I don't know if I'd say big-time, but...
...he's in a band, right?
Huh?
Oh...
...yeah, I guess so.
Your 31-year-old self...
...is actually a musician.
Huh.
I'M SO COOL!
Okay...
...I'm heading out.
See ya!
Wait!
Huh?
So, this sure is some turn of fate, huh?
For sure!
I knew that if someone was gonna write a song for our town...
...it had to be you.
And then coincidence struck as I just happened to be looking through your concert videos...
...and I saw my old friend in your backup band!
Hey, Shino!
That hurt.
This performance will be Shinosuke's triumphant homecoming.
We should be sure to feature his guitar solo.
Oh, sweet!
Can there be a saxophone solo, too?
Yeah, your sax doesn't really have that punch we need.
You know what I mean?
Hey, what do you mean by punch?
So, did you tell Aoi that Shino was coming home?
Hmm?
Did you just say something, Akane?
Hey, hey, hey!
Is something going on between you two?
Huh?
How about we just leave that to the imagination, okay?
Stop, Michinko!
What did I say?
Ugh!
The beer's already gone flat.
Can I get the high-end stuff?
Oh!
And more meat, please.
Hmm...
Maybe...
...he's a ghost tied to the shrine hall?
Yeah, like he knows he's trapped but still tries to leave.
Your wildest dreams will come true.
Back then, I really believed it.
Couldn't wait to graduate and move to Tokyo.
I wanted the future to start right then,
so I could come back and carry her away.
I needed to make that happen as soon as I could.
So I think that, even if I am some kind of living spirit,
I wasn't born out of hatred.
Anyway, I don't really get any of this,
but I do know one thing.
If Akane and future me get together,
that'll fix everything!
Problem solved!
Because then I, the spirit,
would return to my main body like,
whoosh!
And done!
Ugh!
I'm counting on you, Eyeball Star!
Hmm?
Did he always act like this?
Hmm...
Yeah, kinda.
But back then, he did seem more mature.
What are you gonna do?
Hmm?
Are you gonna do what Shino says
and try to get older him and Akane back together again?
It might not be a bad idea.
Ugh, really?
Maybe.
I mean,
it might be better than...
Hakane feeling tied to this place.
And to me.
Come on, let's go for another round.
Round two!
Yeah, great idea, sir.
Come on, Shinosuke.
If you're gonna barf,
you gotta do it in the toilet.
That was some tasty meat.
Oh man, this guy's pretty racked.
Look at him.
I guess it can't be helped.
I didn't drink anything,
so I can drive him.
Huh?
Hey, Masamichi.
How about we go someplace that has girls?
Come on, time to go.
I wanna see some local beauties.
Ah, sounds great.
Huh?
Pandora, huh?
Oh, you're up.
Yeah, I guess.
So, my dreams came true, kind of.
Yeah, I really think they did.
Are you making fun of me?
You know,
I wouldn't have guessed
you'd be so bad at holding your liquor.
Awful.
I hear you're still single.
Were you waiting for me?
Hmm.
Waiting for you?
No.
I don't think so.
Here we are.
Come in.
Watch your step.
I'll bring you water.
Hey, how about we have another drink?
Stop it.
That's ridiculous.
Come on.
Uh.
You can't afford to play hard again at your age.
Are you serious?
What?
Not like you have anything to lose.
Is this really what you wanna say?
After 13 years?
Don't disappoint me.
What?
You can't afford to play hard again at your age.
No.
No, you can't afford to play hard again at your age.
me it's not like i wanted to come back here i didn't want not like this hi i'm home ollie
uh welcome back that was fast really well i don't have the stamina to stay out all night with the
gas i'm skipping my bath gonna head straight to bed hey do you want to have a sleepover huh come on
it's been a while hey what can you tell me about your old boyfriend shinosuke hmm well now he's just
a drunk not today tell me how he was back then that was so long ago i don't even remember
my memory has always been terrible
but you never had another boyfriend after him well i did have a little something
no way you never said anything about that how many more secrets are you keeping
owie you better be careful or i might think you love me
no that's not
i don't care
delicious
hey you really don't mind me eating your lunch i'll just grab something later
okay sounds good
oh i'm just surprised you can feel hunger
i mean it's not like real hunger i don't know anyway i'm just bored out of my mind
you got a guitar you could always nah the strings are rusted want me to get new ones nickel strings
no need
seriously don't worry about it but could you get me the latest issue of jump
i gotta read my kochikame or i'll be out of the loop
kochikame ended a while ago
what but kochikame can't ever end
but he was gone
there's nothing eternal
i really don't know
so who did he end up with
wait
at least he's taking this all seriously
oh
whoa is that michinko
did he really look like this
i get why shino calls sugu his miniature
akane
so they were in the same high school class
he's like a little kid
what about akane
that's the kind of thing i would write
but knows
the blueness of the sky
huh
iowy
so remember how you said you'd get back to us
about joining our band
playing with weaker musicians is just a waste of my time
what did you say bitch
wow that girl is pretty harsh
what a waste
being the only girl in a boy band
is a great opportunity
uh but i get it
you pretend not to care about that
tokyo is waiting after all
and that hot older guy you've been seeing
it's a rumor you know
that some guy picks you up after school every day
hey you think you could introduce me to his friends
i promise i'll play it cool
even if i end up heartbroken
hmm
yeah okay
want to tag along right now
next up let's discuss the budget for the state
hang on before that
what's this budget for mr nitobi to find a local love
oh yeah that's just
it's a funny story
see it's this
ah that shaved ice place is pretty popular huh
18 000 yen just for shaved ice
he said he had to try out all the different ice flavors in order to really feel the heart energy of the shop owner
my god i hope they all get diarrhea
oh that's nagatoro
so they're down river now
they're probably having chestnut soba with miso pork
how much can this guy eat
akane
what's up
you're mad at me
aren't you
of course i am
it would be weird if i weren't
like i told you last night the whole shino thing came as a surprise to me too
i found out when i offered nitobe the songwriting gig i promise
but also i figured that if you didn't get some closure you'd always feel attached to shinosuke
drop the act
what
how could you have so little regard for my independence
i have always been my own person
i have spent my entire life making my own choices and my own decisions
no one can take away my autonomy
and that's that
so does your boyfriend have a full-time job
are any of his friends students
i mean i wouldn't mind
this girl is such an airhead
but her relentless positivity
kind of reminds me of michinko
is he here
who's that
is that a friend
hello
bummer turns out it's just my sister
what attacked by a deer
a deer
right ito the drummer and kodama the bassist both got food poisoning
it was the best thing i ever ate
absolutely no regrets
you should have regrets
they said to cook it thoroughly didn't they
if i waited any longer he would have eaten it all
look who's talking
these guys are real actual rock stars
i can totally feel the vibes
what
i don't think they can make the festival
we do have the backing tracks
the worst case scenario
you can perform without the live music
impossible
i reject that
ah mr nitobe
music is alive
it is the very heart of life
so without live music
i wouldn't be channeling the soul of inca
i dankichi nitobe
absolutely refuse to perform at the soulless heartless pre-recorded backing track
but sir
i'm not sure we can find musicians so last minute
so the band is short a drummer and a bassist right
uh yeah that's right
i have a solution
i know a drummer
and a bassist
huh
what the hell
it's total nonsense
a high school girl and a city hall worker are gonna fill in
i think that sounds fun
oh it sucks
but you know nitobe's really pumped about the whole idea
he's even gone off to city hall to pitch it to them
oh no
how could this be happening to me
i don't want to be associated with this kid stuff
unlike these guys i'm an actual pro
did you forget i'm an eyeball star
huh
i'll see what's kid stuff
after you hear me play
hey owie
good idea
what
all right
let's see what they've got
huh
hit it me chinko
whoa they're pretty good
hmm not bad at all
but why do you think kandara
oh wow
she wrote this
there's superb
you can really feel the passion
i can see it now
this is gonna be the highlight of the festival
holy crap
that's so incredible al
being part of a professional backing band at your age
well things just sort of turned out this way
yeah
turned out great
if you're playing in a band with present day shino
that means akane is gonna be spending time with him
exactly
we finally have the chance to bring the two of us together
am i right
but
i don't know if i can do it
these guys
are pros
of course you can
don't you remember who you are
an eyeball star like me
okay
time to get practicing
you got the score right
uh um yeah
hey
ollie
are you in there
hmm
what are you doing
huh
oh uh nothing
what are you doing
oh
um
i wanted to
say sorry
for pushing you to do this
oh
i just
pictured you
playing on that big stage
and i had to
it's okay
i mean i'm
um
i'm actually
getting kinda excited about it
that's great
hey i brought you snacks
you two can share
all right then
don't stay up too late okay
oh
good thing we managed to hide her
yeah
jump scared
she's an old lady now
huh
i guess
but she's the prettiest damn old lady ever
to me she's
even more beautiful than any bikini idol
or runway model
hey uh
you okay
what
why wouldn't i be
hakenay's been through a lot
and for much longer
huh
for me
we just broke up yesterday
but akane's been alone for 13 years
i want to make her happy
as soon as i possibly can
that's really sweet
anyway
i bet my future self has gotten really good at guitar by now
technically
yeah
yes
if you want me to record him
i could
huh
with this
how's that even possible
those smartphones are wild
that game you showed me earlier was crazy
hey do you think i could keep it overnight
no absolutely not
here you can take mine
what
are you sure
totally
it's just one night
and the only people who ever call me are akana and sugu
okay
here's my passcode
don't tell him that
you freaking rock al
you've grown up to be awesome
hey
come on
don't pat my head like that
hey
are you actually gonna do it
record him
yeah why
because if he sees his current self
he might be really disappointed
you really think so
i do
shino might be stupid
but he's a nice guy
and he doesn't look down on people
also
what is it
nothing
uh
why are you here
you guys are gonna need footage of shinosuke right
well leave it to me
i'm great at filming
i can do other stuff for you too
you know like an assistant
sorry but she was already waiting by the time i got here
i mean it can't hurt to have another videographer right
you got the right idea there little guy
oh here you are
we're gonna start rehearsal pretty soon
so go ahead and set up
okay
okay guys great job well done
shinosuke is so true
what was that
hmm
you gotta be kidding
do you even know what you're doing
what
you're just a bassist
why were you trying to stand out like that
i'm sorry i didn't know
god a chick really shouldn't be playing a bass guitar to begin with
okay then
okay then now you're gonna grow up and become our bassist
their hands and bodies are too small they can't keep the rhythm
okay hey now we're amateurs and this is our first time so try to overlook some of our
problems start when amateurs try and dabble in the professional world
it's your fault too
you're dragged down by the bass so we all got thrown off
if the drummer can't keep the rhythm then we're all screwed
hey
shinosuke
there he is
wow huge space
hey ankle
hey
hello sheen
uh um hey there
i guess they're here to pick you up
mr nitobe has already gone ahead to the club
look at you
the pros sure do get the special treatment huh
no i mean
come on sheen
oh so he's a party boy huh
well i guess that's where we call it for today
you texting someone over there
oh i was just sending the rehearsal video over to aoli's phone
you
what
my god you
stupid asshole
uh oh he saw it
what is wrong with this pathetic old loser
he's seriously going to a hostess club
if this is what he's like
akane can't be alone with him
we've got to reinvent him before we try setting them up with her
but on the upside
i guess i really did
become a pro guitar player
damn it that guy's such an idiot
he tries to act so cool but he's got an outie billy button
does he really
yeah
here you want to see it
ah no thanks
okay fine it looks like
it's your time to shine
what
you're gonna show up be totally awesome put on a kick-ass performance and rip this guy's ego to shreds
you ready
i i don't know if i can
i know you can i believe in you trust me you're an eyeball star
hmm
i think i think i have an app on my smartphone on your smartphone that thing really is insane
that thing really is insane
so if shino returns to shinosuke's body does that mean shino will
the role of a bassist is maintaining a consistently accurate rhythm
and supporting the entire band
and supporting the entire band even if the harmony is absolutely falling apart
you're listening to all the other instruments but you gotta hold on to your own tempo
what
shinosuke isn't coming in today
why not the festival's just around the corner
well cut him some slack we haven't scheduled a rehearsal today
and besides uh he said he'll lose his touch if he starts practicing with amateurs
wow he sucks
i've had enough of him looking down on us
he's a totally different person than shino
what could have turned him into such a
wait shino
yeah it's shinosuke's nickname from way back
oh
no
shinosuke and shino are not the same person
what
hey nakamura
oh
the room's open now
okay
come on kiddo
let's go practice
we gotta get good at keeping the rhythm
or else this won't work
okay i know i know
hmm
so shino isn't shinosuke huh
whatever i don't care
if he's not here i'm out
that guitar solo sounds amazing
yeah really good
you can play like that
wish it's too fast
all right
don't care
Nice. Now, one more time.
Hey, are you okay? You've been practicing for a really long time.
Didn't you just come from some kind of rehearsal tonight with Machinko?
It's fine.
It's almost nine o'clock, you know.
This is a huge opportunity. I just need a little more time.
Don't you have homework to do?
It doesn't matter. I'm not going to university, anyway.
Oh, yeah? Then what's next?
I'm moving to Tokyo to start my own band.
Wow! You're following in my footsteps! That's so awesome!
Okay, well, don't get too excited or anything.
I kind of have another motive.
What do you mean?
Well, the real reason I want to get out of this town is Akane.
I want her to live her own life.
And I think she's been holding herself back because of me.
I'm keeping her from doing the things she wants to do.
If I stay, she'll have something tying her here for the rest of her life.
It's not like I have a clear idea of what I'm going to do with my future.
But I don't want Akane picking up the slack for me.
I don't want to cause her any more trouble than I already have.
That's a lot of pressure to put on yourself.
I'm sure nobody sees you as a burden.
No, everybody sees me that way.
The ladies in the neighborhood, her relatives.
How?
That's just how it is.
Which is why I have got to get out on my own.
You're amazing, you know that?
I've had a lot of time to try and puzzle out how and why I wound up back here.
I might be a living spirit, but I don't think it's because I'm still dwelling on the past.
I think that the reason that I'm here is because deep down I'm afraid of leaving this place.
That's partly why I'm so impressed by you.
I know you have so much on your mind.
But you've thought it through.
And you've made the decision.
You're okay with leaving.
What?
That's in return for the other day.
In return? What are you talking about?
A basis job is to support everyone.
You got that right.
That's what I want to hear from my future bassist.
Huh?
Well, hold on.
This is the future.
That must mean-
Do you really remember saying that?
Huh?
It's not exactly something you just forget.
We made a promise.
Don't you play bass because you're keeping our promise?
Hmm?
Kate, go ahead. Just do it.
What do you want? Am I supposed to pat your head?
Flick my forehead. Don't be shy. Do it.
Jeez.
Just remember, you asked for it.
Yep. Don't hold back.
Here I come.
Okay, bye.
See you tomorrow.
It worked.
Ow.
Okay, bye.
See you tomorrow.
It worked.
Ow.
Okay, so this is definitely a wrench in the gears.
But I can't let it change things. I have to bring Akane and Shinosuke together. For Akane's sake.
And for Shino's too.
Okay, good morning.
Good morning.
We'll come off.
Okay, so this is definitely a wrench in the gears.
But I can't let it change things.
I have to bring Akane and Shinosuke together.
For Akane's sake.
And for Shinos too.
Okay, good morning.
I just heard that Chico was with some guy yesterday.
Seriously?
I know, right?
Apparently, she was with this really hot older guy.
An older guy?
Yeah.
It sounds like he was totally gorgeous.
I wonder if he's rich.
Oh, well, hi there.
How's it going?
Uh, huh?
Wait!
That hurts!
Ow!
Get off of me!
Huh?
The guy.
The one you were with yesterday.
Uh, yeah, Shinosuke?
What about him?
You suck.
Um, excuse me?
It almost sounds like you have a crush on him or something.
I definitely do not!
The one I like is Shino!
Come on, I love a cute guy and all but I would never steal my friend's crush.
And you said Shino and Shinosuke aren't the same person.
That's right.
So, you have a crush on this guy, Shino.
Yeah!
I like him!
Uh, why are you being so weird right now?
And so what?
I mean, no one said anything!
Whoa!
Hey, what's going on?
Hey!
This is all wrong!
I'm not...
Supposed to...
Are...
Are you gonna be okay?
Hmm...
Huh?
Uh...
Did I forget to lock the door this morning?
Huh?
Uh...
Ah!
Ollie?
My gosh, you scared me.
Hey, you should really tell me when you come home early.
I tried calling you several times but you didn't pick up.
Why didn't you go with him?
Hmm?
With Shino.
Why didn't you go with Shinosuke?
What?
Why are you bringing that up?
If you'd gone to Tokyo with him...
Then maybe...
He wouldn't have grown up to become such a scumbag.
He might have...
Stayed the way he was back then.
Oh, uh...
What is this really about?
I don't want...
To wake up one day and be you, Akane!
You always hold yourself back.
And then you regret it.
No!
I won't let that be my life.
I won't stay here!
I refuse!
Nothing's gonna keep me here!
Oh, my God.
This isn't what I wanted to say.
You're just so...
You look like...
And I feel like...
And just am...
An idiot!
I'm an idiot.
Hey, please wait! Don't go!
assaulted me!
Uh...
Uhh...
Uh!
Now...
Oh, it's open.
Ali?
Are you in here?
So, she's afraid of turning out like me.
All right.
Man, Kelp again.
Ugh.
I'm realizing all over again
that I am
just a truly terrible person.
You are.
It's pretty terrible that you made me trudge all the way to go fetch your base,
and then you just showed up at my house without warning,
acting like you own the place and disrupting my entire night like I don't have a life.
Ugh.
Okay, but admit that Shinosuke is a thousand times worse than I am.
Sit up, Al. Your undies are out.
That's it.
Hey, Al. Maybe calm down a bit first.
Michinko.
Huh?
Get up and get it together,
because I'm going to help you win over Akane.
Oh, okay. You'll help.
Huh?
What?
Come on, Dad. Not so loud. The neighbors.
Uh, didn't you say you were against the idea of your sister marrying a divorcee?
Well, I've had some time to reflect,
and a divorcee is still better than Shinosuke.
Hey, thanks.
Really.
But your help isn't necessary.
Uh...
I decided to ask Nitobe to do this job after I found out
that Shinosuke was working with him.
Huh?
I figured that if we ever wanted to move on,
we had some things to settle.
Akane and I were both
at a particular stage in life.
Huh?
That's cold!
Hey, what's gotten into you?
Pathetic.
You disgust me.
Adults are so unbelievably lame.
And your belly's hairy!
Huh?
Jeez, don't hold back.
Sugu, buddy.
Could you maybe go grab your old man a towel or something?
Sugu!
Okay, be careful.
Akane?
Huh?
Where should I put this thing?
Oh, I can take it from you.
Thanks for your help
and for giving up a Saturday.
No problem.
It's not like I'm in any school club,
so I've got plenty of time.
The festival's only two days away,
so go ahead and put me to work.
Oh.
Over here!
Owie!
Hey!
Looks like she's still ignoring me.
Hello.
Hmm?
The lighting tech is looking for you
so he can confirm your stage position.
Oh, sure.
Thank you.
And he's also looking for Shinosuke,
who seems to have disappeared.
Ah, yeah.
Don't worry.
I'm happy to take care of it for him instead.
Oh.
You sure?
This is the town he grew up in, right?
I'm sure he's got all sorts of things to attend to.
Does he now?
I've been playing back up my whole career,
but he's already made his solo debut.
Though I guess he hasn't released anything since.
Hmm.
Is that so?
Password.
Motoyama.
Hey, what's up?
I thought you were helping with festival prep.
Yeah, but first I needed to come and talk to you about something.
Hmm?
I think I might have feelings for Aoi.
She's my first crush.
Um, what?
It's weird that you're the one blushing right now.
What?
Blushing me?
I'm totally not.
That's...
You...
Have mature taste in girls.
Well, maybe for now.
But later on,
when I'm an adult with a job and stuff,
our age gap will seem pretty insignificant.
Or at least I think so.
Um, well, I guess...
When you put it like that.
Anyway,
I'm gonna study really hard and get good grades.
Since she really hates school,
I want to be a good student for both of us
and prove to myself that I'm worthy of her.
I see.
Wow.
I'm so impressed.
The thing is,
I think I have a rival.
What?
Well, who is it?
Hmm?
Huh?
What?
Now,
you tell me.
How do you feel about her?
Hey, wait a second.
Suku, calm down.
I'm very calm.
You're the one freaking out.
Hmm.
How I feel, huh?
I mean,
from my perspective,
I just got dumped by Akane the other day.
And I thought of Aoi as a little kid
until very recently.
More importantly,
I'm just Shinosuke's living spirit
and it's not like I can even...
Falling for someone like me
wouldn't be good for her.
Yeah,
I agree.
So...
Hey,
come on!
How much longer
are you gonna ignore me?
Oh.
Get away from me,
Chica the Desperate.
Whoa.
That's a pretty savage nickname.
I told you,
we didn't actually
do anything that night.
Do you actually expect me
to believe that?
It's pretty obvious to me
that this scumbag
plus a desperate you
equals illicit secret love affair.
He's the one who disappointed me
if you can believe that.
He turned out to be such a square.
He was a total coward.
When am I gonna find
my Prince Charming
to sweep me off my feet
and carry me far away?
Otakee.
Oh.
About the reception forms
you gave you earlier.
I'm sorry, sir.
I put them on that one cart
over there by the entrance.
You put them on that one cart.
Thank you.
Why'd you stop?
Keep going.
I guess I really believe that all my dreams would come true if I just moved to Tokyo.
But turns out I was wrong.
You weren't. Your dreams did come true. You make a living playing guitar.
It wasn't exactly my dream to be a member of an Anka singer's backup band.
But...
It's not that I'm complaining.
I'm very grateful to Mr. Nitobe.
I feel lucky just to have a career in music.
I just... don't know if leaving here was worth it in the end.
I gave up things that were precious to me.
Can I put in a request for a different song?
Huh?
Could you play Her Blue Sky?
How did it?
I bought it, of course. It was your solo debut single.
That's from my dark past.
I actually happen to like that song. As much as Gandara, even.
Hmm.
Oh yeah.
全然好きじゃなかった
ほら映画と
キャラメル味のキス
全然好きになれなかった
それなのにね
今は悲鳴を上げながら
君の横顔を探してる
短吉にとべスター
君教な心の落とし穴
暗すぎて何も見えない
Come on, what are you doing?
Okay, now, I'll do it like your best as I to our math teacher
君教えにしとくもやりのみた
Akane. She looks so… I've only ever seen Akane laugh like that. With… Shino. It's him.
All right. Thank you for listening.
I've got a cramp. Next time I'm gonna make you sing it right for me, just so you know.
You know, I still like being around you, even after all this time. I feel so at peace.
What?
I'm considering moving back here. It's not like I see a bright future with my current gig.
Don't.
It's been tough, you know. Everyone around me is starting to find a steady job. To settle down.
I'm not getting any younger, so maybe it's time for a change.
Don't. If you do this, I'm gonna lose Shino.
What are you talking about? These days, your early thirties isn't even that old. It's not like when we were kids.
I don't think there's any hurry to settle down yet.
Yeah?
There's still so much I want to get done, and I gotta do it here. I still have goals that I haven't given up on.
Yep. This is just the beginning.
Maybe so.
Definitely so.
Yeah, you're right.
Hmm.
You heading back?
Mm-hmm. I should probably get going. See ya.
Mm-hmm.
So that's what it looks like when Akane cries.
I had no idea when was the last time I saw her cry.
Akane, can you get my lo-
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Ah.
Mm-hmm.
Ah!
Ah.
Oh, a strategy handbook.
Mm-hmm.
Ah.
Ah!
Come here, Arie.
Are you okay?
Yes!
Ah.
Hey, little miss.
If you have nothing else to do, how about helping me out a bit?
What? No! You're super good at frying stuff!
Do you think the ingredients yell yum when you fry them because they know they taste good?
Maybe they do.
I didn't know how much I was putting her through.
I'd always just assumed that Akonhae could handle anything.
But the reason, she always seemed so perfect.
It was that the whole time,
she was working so hard to take good care of me.
And now I...
What's wrong with me?
What am I even doing?
What am I?
What the hell?
It's you.
You should have set the password.
Don't scare me like that.
I have a crush on you, Shino.
Oh, well, I'm really touched to hear that.
But you should think this over.
I'm a living spirit and...
Stop talking!
What?
Because your voice is so...
sounds so gentle.
People with voices that kind
are usually trying to console you
or pity you or let you down easy.
Huh?
And even if that's not what you're trying to do,
your voice just sounds so sweet
and so warm
that it makes my heart ache.
So I don't want to hear it.
Please, just let me say everything I'm feeling right now.
I have a crush on you, Shino.
I have a crush on the Shino
who's here now
and not on Shinosuke.
I want to be with you.
And that can't happen
if you turn back into Shinosuke.
I want you to stay like this.
Look out.
But then...
I have...
to think
about my sister.
And Akane...
I know in my heart
that she still loves Shinosuke.
I have to think of Akane's happiness.
That means that you, Shino...
I really don't know what to do.
Please, help me decide.
Don't touch me!
What?
Why?
Because if you touch me,
it'll just make everything worse!
Well, okay.
In that case,
what am I supposed to do?
Oh, so you don't know either!
How the hell would I know?
Fine!
Just forget it!
What?
Wait, ow!
I said wait!
Please, wait up!
I'm begging you!
Please, just stop.
You know I can't...
run after you.
I really, really wish that I could.
But I can't.
All I can do is stand here
and watch you go.
I have...
no idea what'll happen
once I merge back
with my future self.
I hate...
the fact that I can't
do anything
to stop you from crying
and walking away
from me like this.
I'm not crying.
I'm not crying!
It's just the rain!
Why am I even here?
Should I bother asking
why?
what the hell is going on?
No!
Hey, morning.
Good morning.
So, um, about yesterday.
I'm sorry.
Uh, oh, no, no, there's no need to apologize.
I get that I was being kind of annoying.
It's fine.
But I...
Stop, stop.
Don't worry about it.
It's gone!
Mr. Nietobe, what's wrong?
What's gone?
The pendant.
The pendant I always wear.
It's gone.
What pendant is he talking about?
Oh, yeah, that tacky necklace.
That pendant acts as my spirit totem.
It contains heart energy from the thousands of fans I've met all over the world.
Really?
I cannot possibly tap into the local spirit without that pendant.
And I certainly can't sing the soul of Inca without it.
What?
A dramatic speech.
He's done this a few times.
Oh.
Mr. Nietobe, sorry, sir.
It's not in the car either.
Oh!
Calm down.
Let's just think.
Do you remember where you were the last time you were wearing it?
Huh?
The last time?
How about...
Let's see.
Oh, that's Water Ruins.
He's wearing it.
This is...
At Mitsumine Shrine, maybe?
This guy's having too much fun.
I mean, look.
There are so many photos of him with his arm around some lady.
What?
I was just having a touching moment with the local.
The photos after this are all from yesterday.
Oh, look at that.
He stops wearing the pendant after this photo.
Oh, you're right.
So that must mean...
The last place he was wearing it was...
Right here.
Oh, the tunnel.
It had a certain ambience about it.
There was a fence in front, but I just hopped on over it.
That's the spot.
Oh, well, I guess that makes sense.
It did feel a lot like a survival game.
Okay, then.
I'll look for it there.
Huh?
Are you sure?
Please get ready for rehearsal, sir.
Oh, uh, Akane, be careful out there!
Do your best.
Well, then, let's trust that my pendant will be returned to me.
And with hopeful spirits, let us now turn our focus to the task at hand.
We must not let the locals down.
Their hearts and souls are with us.
We can't afford to take any more breaks.
This guy treats his whole life like one big break.
Hey, where's Shinosuke anyway?
He, uh, said he had some place he needed to be.
He'll join us later.
Seriously?
Huh?
Oh, gosh.
Oh, boy.
What was he even doing out here?
Huh?
Was that a quake?
Ah!
You didn't feel that?
Really?
Yes.
I thought it was shaking just now.
Did you?
Huh.
Yes.
I don't see any reports yet.
What?
Huh?
Okay, yes, I understand.
Thank you.
Did they say what happened?
There's been a landslide in the Hino area.
We have to go issue a warning from the tourism division.
They're telling me to hurry back.
A landslide?
My goodness.
Yeah, um, it happened up in the mountains.
No major structural damage has been reported so far.
Oh, I see.
See, I told you that was an earthquake.
I guess that's good news.
It rained really hard yesterday, so...
Wait, the Hino area?
Isn't Akane going to the tunnel over there?
What?
Akane!
Oh, wait.
Calm down.
Call her.
See if you can reach her.
No!
It's not going through!
Hey, hey.
You need to remain calm.
Negativity won't help the situation.
Positivity, yeah?
Think positive.
Oh, please.
Like you're one to talk.
I have to head to City Hall now.
I'll let you know as soon as there's an update.
Everyone stay here.
So, Mr. Nitobe, I have to leave you.
My apologies.
Of course.
Please, be careful.
All right, then.
Sugu, I'm counting on you.
Okay.
Ow.
What?
Hey, wait!
I'm outside, so just bring the car around to me.
Huh?
Hey!
Ow!
Hey, where are you going?
How?
It's me.
From high school?
Oh, I get it.
You're here to get the Akane special back.
Huh?
How'd you...
Your precious guitar that you worked so hard and saved up for that Akane helped you pick out,
and yet it's been rotting here for years.
Pathetic.
Look, I get that your dreams didn't come true, but do you have to be so angry and bitter?
A brat like you wouldn't understand anything.
I don't want to understand anything, some sad old slob thinks.
Why, you...
Hmm.
Shin...
What?
Shinosuke?
Why are you...
Are you okay, Al?
Shino, I need help!
It's Akane!
A landslide?
It happened just now?
And Akane got caught in?
We still don't know.
Michinko's still trying to figure that out.
I'm hoping she's okay, but I can't get a hold of her, and I'm kind of freaking out right now.
Ah, jeez.
You scared me for a second.
So, we just have to sit tight and wait for Michinko's call.
Why are you so calm?
Hmm?
How can you just stand there and do nothing?
What do you mean?
You have to go find Akane right now!
She could be hurt!
Why the hell aren't you doing anything?
Because me going there now won't...
You're...
Oh, you okay?
You should be the one out there saving her!
Oh my god, you're so disappointing!
Shit!
You said you'd become a famous musician, then come back and take Akane away from here!
But you're just in some backup band for an Inca singer.
I can't believe you!
Shut up!
You're pathetic!
So damn pathetic!
The thought of it makes me want to puke!
Knowing you're the guy I'm gonna become!
I told you to shut it!
Akane, stop it!
You think I'm not trying?
I'm working my hardest every day!
Yeah, getting better at guitar all for nothing.
You could have done anything with that kind of technical skill.
All that matters in this industry are luck and connections.
You can't just coast on skill alone.
You're being an ignorant little brat.
You're right!
I am totally ignorant!
I've been stuck here all these years.
What?
But she knows.
That day, when Akane told me she wasn't coming to Tokyo, it hit me really hard.
It was my dream to go to Tokyo, put together a band, play lots of live shows, and make my debut.
Every day in adventure, all those dreams coming true.
But that was supposed to happen with Akane there with me, by my side.
So I vowed to get famous and then come back for Akane, but I was never really sure.
When the time came, a part of me said, I don't want to go anywhere.
I want to keep things just the way they are.
Stay.
But you did it anyway.
You actually pushed yourself forward!
Come on.
Reassure me.
I'm going to become you, aren't I?
Then you've got to sell it to me!
I get that.
Certain things aren't going to work out for us.
But I've got to know, becoming you isn't going to be so bad.
Tell me it won't be so bad!
I, uh...
Forget it!
Chino!
I'm getting out of here!
I said, I'm getting out of here!
Well, straight places, you can stay trapped in here, being old!
Why, Art?
Time might have stopped for me, but my feelings for Akane have only grown stronger.
They've never stopped.
That's the one thing I have that you can never change!
Never!
Me, too!
I love her, too!
I care about her more than you ever could!
I'm pretty sure I distinctly remember you telling me not to touch you!
Jake!
Ah!
There you go.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
What the heck just happened?
All right.
Huh?
We're gonna go now.
What are you gonna do, Grandpa?
What...
What am I gonna do?
I'm...
Let's go, Al!
Uh!
Wait!
What?
Hey, stop!
Wait!
You think you can talk to me like that?!
Slow down!
Hang on!
What?
Huh?
Ah!
We're coming for you, Akane!
They're flying?
What the hell?
This is upsetting!
Ah!
So cool!
How is this even possible?
How can I go?
You're the one going in!
Ah!
There isn't a single texture on here!
I hate this country side!
Ah!
he's feeling the same things i feel things he didn't want to fester and turn into regrets
i mean like i said you will have to wait until we can confirm that it's safe for you to drive
up from here you should go back to the road and drive right forget it here keep the change what
hey you're saying cars can't go up right then i'll just wait shino is that you
huh hey it's me abu oh man it's been forever have you been back long sorry i'm in a rush no time to
chat hey wait a minute where you running to that's why i was stuck in that place
regret i know what that feels like
if you don't give the people you love the support they deserve
it can lead to a lifetime of regret
i know that because i wasn't supporting akane
uh how but i can change it now by doing my best to help shino and shinosuke
stop what was that for
well i just i heard that babies stop crying if you blow on their foreheads
you're so weird
shut up
the sky it's so blue
i wanted to get out of here so desperately
but i never noticed how beautiful it is
yeah
it's beautiful
oh
found you
you sure are
a little troublemaker
do you realize where you are right now
you've always had nerves of steel
shino
there you are
where's
shino
hirakane
i see
this is so bizarre
and it's very you
so you think i'm real
i mean you're here in front of me
aren't you
seriously there's nothing that can shake you is there
actually
i like it this way
because it's dark in here
if you saw me in the light
you'd see how old i look
you'd probably be disappointed
hate to break it to you
but i've already seen how you look
wait you have
when where
in the shrine hall
when you came to check on ao
you were bringing her rice balls
god
seriously
yeah
they were kelp again right
the rice balls
no matter how much i begged for tuna mayo
you always made them with kelp
because they're her favorite
yeah sorry
don't apologize
i get it now
a frog in a well
is ignorant of the vast sea
but it knows
the blueness of the sky
that's still your favorite quote
you remember
tuna mayo can't possibly be kelp can it
not when you're focused on the blueness of the sky
she's so pretty now isn't she
i don't know
she's gotten a lot taller
but she's anti-social
kind of clumsy
and a little bit clueless
but also
she's honest and knows what's right
yeah
she's honest
been a little clueless
i guess that makes her
a little like you
i'm glad
you're the kind of person
who puts your little sister's well-being
above everything else
and i am so thankful
that i got the chance to love you
i said don't
don't know whether or not it's stable yet
don't try unless you can fly in
let me go
akane's in there
what are you guys doing
you're so heavy
what that's rude
whatever are you all right
yeah i'm totally fine
you're always such a warrior
not just me
everybody was freaking out
i'm sorry
i'm sorry i made you worry
you did
you really did
what you're going back alone
yeah
really
how come
all of us can fit in here
oh no it'll be
way too cramped
with four people
i'll catch a taxi
somewhere on the way
oh well if that's the case
i can just
no
the three of you should go
are we
bye
shina
yeah
thanks for everything
eyeball star
this kid
he's asleep
it's okay
he's worn out from trying to save me
you know i
according to this guy
i'm actually moving forward in life
what
but i'm still only at the midpoint
i'm reminding myself that this is just the midpoint
so i
shouldn't
give up yet
yeah
and i'm not
i'm not giving up on you either akane
hmm
uh
oh
the three of you
that's right
ali is
just about the same age
as i was back then
next time
i'll make some tuna mayo rice balls
how's that sound
huh
what
so hey does that mean
oh
i'm not
these
if
they
go
I'm not.
Stupid, she know it.
Wow, the sky.
It's so damn blue.
Thank you.
この大空の青さを 瞳のパレットに 潜らせて包み込んで 涙さえも味方に
きっと僕たちが想像した未来は ガラスの靴や魔女が飛び交う絵本のような物語
変な理由もなくと信じていたんだ
Hey baby なんておどけて笑い 汗かいて大人になった
知らない間 見つぶされそうな幸せ あのに芽吹く花が
どうか最後まで咲きますように 全てを光らせ
さよなら あの日の 少年の夢よ
また会おうか まだただいま 言えるくらいの余裕あるだろう
この大空の青さを 心の明日にして泳いで
潜り込んで また帰っておいで
だから今は さよなら 少年の影を
また会おうな まだただいま 言える場所はとっておくぜ
この大空の青さを 瞳のパレットに 潜らせて 包み込んで
涙さえも味方に
ご視聴ありがとうございました
チャンネル登録よろしくお願いします